Vandit Parikh

Accountant Assistant

Motivated and detail-oriented professional with 10 years of experience in bookkeeping, audit and preparation of financial statements and taxation. Seeking a challenging position where can utilize skills and experience to contribute to the success of the organization

Work History

2016-01 -Current

Account Manager

K A Shah and Co., Vadodara

- Performing financial accounting and reporting for firms and companies include preparing balance sheets, organizing data for GST and TDS filling, finalizing accounts as well conducting audits for both firms and listed companies as team lead.
- Performing tally based accounting for Sardar Sarovar Narmada Nigam Ltd. (Channi) and Kevadiya independently.

2014-07 -2015-12

Account Assisstant

Dazzy Food Industries/Vadodara/July 2014-December 2015, Vadodara Creating sales bills, maintaining stock register, and organizing data for balance sheet. Leading month-end close process, including preparing journal entries and analyzing financial statements for accuracy.

2013-06 -2014-06

Account Assistant

Rutvi Associates, Vadodara

Preparing monthly data for return filling and doing tally accounts and preparing monthly data for monthly or quarterly return filling under Income tax and GST act.

2010-01 -

Account Assistant

2013-05

K A Shah and Co., Vadodara Involved in preparation of income tax returns of

Contact

Address

Vadodara, Gujarat 390025

Phone

+91 9099506616

E-mail

vandit.m88@gmail.com

www

https://bold.pro /my/apurva-parikh/613

Skills

Accounting



Taxation (Direct/Indirect)



Book Keeping



Auditing



individuals and firms and performing audit of SME entities and firms along with team.

Education

2006-06 - 2009-06	Bachelor of Commerce: Accounting And Taxation
	Maharaja Sayajirao University of Baroda - Vadodara
2005-06 - 2006-05	12th Standard HSC
	Sayaji Boys High School - Vadodara
2003-06 - 2004-06	10th Standard SSC
	Sayaji Boys High School - Vadodara